<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[A Brief But Stunning Reign of Terror]]></title>
  <link href="http://Sharilyn.github.io/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://Sharilyn.github.io/"/>
  <updated>2013-11-06T18:09:17-05:00</updated>
  <id>http://Sharilyn.github.io/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Sharilyn]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hypersensitivity]]></title>
    <link href="http://Sharilyn.github.io/blog/2013/11/06/hypersensitivity/"/>
    <updated>2013-11-06T17:56:00-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://Sharilyn.github.io/blog/2013/11/06/hypersensitivity</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>30 days of sobriety. Well, 33 now. Honestly, if I&rsquo;d known 10 years ago how much better I&rsquo;d feel without alcohol or marijuana as a part of my life, I think I&rsquo;d have gone straight-edge a long time ago. Overall, I feel so much healthier. Been going to the gym about 5 times per week. Stronger, faster, less hungry, less sad, sleeping better. All good.</p>

<p>But it&rsquo;s not a mystery to me why I started drinking in the first place: I&rsquo;m a very sensitive person. Noise and chaos affects me. Strong smells affect me. The emotional state of the erson sitting next to me affects me. This is a GREAT quality for an artist. This is a TERRIBLE quality for someone who lives in Brooklyn.</p>

<p>Without the sweet oblivious embrace of alcohol to blunt my acute senses, I&rsquo;m pretty much cranky all the time.</p>

<p>BUT when I started to get cranky about Ruby homework, I merely learned to turn my brain around. Instead of holding onto my immediate reaction of OH GOD I DON&rsquo;T KNOW HOW TO DO THIS, instead I remembered that I&rsquo;m good at this stuff and smart enoug to figure it out without too much trouble. I&rsquo;ve always been good at Googling stuff and this turns out to be a very important skills for the beginning web developer.</p>

<p>Finally, journalism training proves good for SOMETHING.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[I may have jacked up git]]></title>
    <link href="http://Sharilyn.github.io/blog/2013/10/28/i-may-have-jacked-up-git/"/>
    <updated>2013-10-28T20:55:00-04:00</updated>
    <id>http://Sharilyn.github.io/blog/2013/10/28/i-may-have-jacked-up-git</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Git confuses me</p>

<p>&ldquo;Your branch is ahead of &lsquo;origin/master&rsquo; by 758 commits.&rdquo;</p>

<p>Ugh I&rsquo;m going to have to read the documentation after all.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Video kills]]></title>
    <link href="http://Sharilyn.github.io/blog/2013/10/28/video-kills/"/>
    <updated>2013-10-28T18:18:00-04:00</updated>
    <id>http://Sharilyn.github.io/blog/2013/10/28/video-kills</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h3>Video Killed the Radio Star</h3>

<p>I had lunch with Michael today, and when we weren&rsquo;t psychoanalysing Seth and Peter, we talked about how difficult it is to ingest a lot of instructional videos. Is it an age thing? I had to drop out of the Code Coalition class because watching video after five-miute video was almost physically painful for me. I ditched out of Code School for the same reason. I think the lack of video is one of the reasons codecademy works so well for me. I&rsquo;d rather follow along with written directions. For some reason that is happier for my brain.</p>

<p>I had to quit that newspaper job. The money was absolutely terrible, so terrible that it didn&rsquo;t even make financial sense to continue. And having one insane job is enough for now.</p>

<p>Twenty-six days of sobriety and I&rsquo;m feeling pretty awesome. The hormone swings are still happening, but not as bad. I didn&rsquo;t get to work out too much this last week but I&rsquo;m still feeling stronger than before. There&rsquo;s something about my body that feels more organized and less foreign now. I haven&rsquo;t lost a size yet but I haven&rsquo;t let that keep me from shopping.</p>

<p>Finished first real homework on time. Though I got my ruby to pass the tests, I&rsquo;m not really sure what or why. I&rsquo;m learning about my own process that I&rsquo;m kind of an instinctive learner, especially with regard to learning language.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[I Finished my Homework]]></title>
    <link href="http://Sharilyn.github.io/blog/2013/10/22/i-finished-my-homework/"/>
    <updated>2013-10-22T21:55:00-04:00</updated>
    <id>http://Sharilyn.github.io/blog/2013/10/22/i-finished-my-homework</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>I don&rsquo;t really know who else to tell, but I FINISHED MY HOMEWORK.</p>

<p>I started a new, second job this week. It&rsquo;s at a newspaper. Newspapering is something I know how to do, it&rsquo;s second nature. But it&rsquo;s also hectic. It&rsquo;s a weekly paper, and today was their close. I was closing for the first time, with the Editor In Chief sitting next to me and grilling me over the photo captions. But, fuck it, we still went to press by 7:30p.</p>

<p>And I only started this job because my first job, at a startup my friends founded, is clearly floundering. It&rsquo;s obvious to everyone that the founders are running out of both money and the will to continue in any useful form. And I can&rsquo;t afford to be jobless in NYC, especially not now since I want to stay through the holidays and learn Ruby and go full stack and be the baddest ass redhead on either side of the Mississippi.</p>

<p>Um and yeah, I quit drinking this month. So there&rsquo;s that.</p>

<p>But I&rsquo;m not here to whine at you. I&rsquo;m here to tell you that I FINISHED MY HOMEWORK.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[So it begins]]></title>
    <link href="http://Sharilyn.github.io/blog/2013/10/21/so-it-begins/"/>
    <updated>2013-10-21T21:10:00-04:00</updated>
    <id>http://Sharilyn.github.io/blog/2013/10/21/so-it-begins</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>So far this is pretty fun. I was looking forward to class tonight and I was not disappointed.</p>

<h3>Tonight we covered</h3>

<ul>
<li>git commands (basic)</li>
<li>command line</li>
<li>committing files</li>
<li>setting up octopress</li>
<li>markdown editing</li>
<li>some blogging</li>
</ul>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
